{"NewQuizID":10,"Quizes":[{"Description":"Test quiz description","Questions":[{"Answers":["Harold Levert","Gerald Levert","Paul Levert","Kanye Levert"],"Question":"Who was Sean Levert's brother, who was part of the group Levert?","CorrectAnswer":1},{"Answers":["Teddy bears","Toy soldiers","Hula hoops","Barbie dolls"],"Question":"American singer-songwriter Martika had her biggest hit in 1988 with a song named after which plaything?","CorrectAnswer":1}],"ID":3,"Name":"Another test quiz"},{"Description":"Seven questions","Questions":[{"Answers":["Max","Joseph","Johannes","Arnold"],"Question":"What was the first name of composer Bruch?","CorrectAnswer":0},{"Answers":["1939","1949","1919","1929"],"Question":"In what year was the National Prohibition Act passed in the USA?","CorrectAnswer":2},{"Answers":["Dutch","Spanish","French","Austrian"],"Question":"What nationality was artist Gustav Klimpt?","CorrectAnswer":3},{"Answers":["Tiger","Snake","Lion","Horse"],"Question":"What creature features on the logo of Alfa Romeo Cars?","CorrectAnswer":1},{"Answers":["Saturn","Mars","Jupiter","Mercury"],"Question":"Phobos and Deimos are moons of which planet?","CorrectAnswer":1},{"Answers":["Iceland","Sweden","Finland","Denmark"],"Question":"In which country is the Parliament called the \"Althingi\"?","CorrectAnswer":0},{"Answers":["Cyprus","Crete","Rhodes","Majorca"],"Question":"Faliraki is located on which Mediterranean island?","CorrectAnswer":2}],"ID":5,"Name":"General Knowledge"},{"Description":"7 general knowledge questions","Questions":[{"Answers":["December","October","November","January"],"Question":"In what month does Remembrance Day occur?","CorrectAnswer":2},{"Answers":["1598","1898","1798","1685"],"Question":"In what year was the artist René Magritte born?","CorrectAnswer":1},{"Answers":["Spotify","Youtube","Facebook","Twitter"],"Question":"The movie \"The Social Network\" was about which social network?","CorrectAnswer":2},{"Answers":["Dan Brown","Charles Dickens","William Shakespeare","Stephen King"],"Question":"Richard Bachmann is a pen name of which famous author?","CorrectAnswer":3},{"Answers":["Exodus","Matthew","Genesis","Romans"],"Question":"Which book of the Bible contains the tale of Noah's flood?","CorrectAnswer":2},{"Answers":["Plum","Figs","Dates","Pomegranate"],"Question":"Grenadine is a syrup that is made from which fruit?","CorrectAnswer":3},{"Answers":["Scrabble","Chess","Poker","Bridge"],"Question":"Magnus Carlsen is, as of 2014, the reigning world champion of what?","CorrectAnswer":1}],"ID":6,"Name":"General Knowledge"},{"Description":"7 computing questions","Questions":[{"Answers":["DNS","DHCP","HTTP","FTP"],"Question":"Which of these services is contacted when a web browser tries to find the IP address from a website's name?","CorrectAnswer":0},{"Answers":["Ada Lovelace","Alan Turing","Claude Shannon","De Moivre"],"Question":"Which contemporary of Charles Babbage is often called the world's first computer programmer?","CorrectAnswer":0},{"Answers":["Richard Branson","Nelson Mandela","Dennis Tito","Mark Shuttleworth"],"Question":"Which South African owns Canonical Ltd., the company behind Ubuntu?","CorrectAnswer":3},{"Answers":["String","Immutable","MemDev()","Mutable"],"Question":"Which type of C++ object can have its elements changed, added to, or removed?","CorrectAnswer":3},{"Answers":["Serial","SATA","FireWire","USB"],"Question":"Of the types listed, what I\/O connection type is chronologically oldest?","CorrectAnswer":0},{"Answers":["Deinit","Dealloc","Demolish","Destroy"],"Question":"In Objective-C, what is the destructor method name?","CorrectAnswer":1},{"Answers":["Anti-virus application","Text editor","Email client","Web browser"],"Question":"What is Mozilla's Thunderbird software an instance of?","CorrectAnswer":2}],"ID":8,"Name":"Computer Science"}]}